dezignwithaz.com 2008-12-17

# Dezign With a Z - Removable Wall Decals - Decorative Modern Stickers for home & office spaces

## • Privacy Policy

**1\. Privacy Policy**  
The [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site is owned and operated by Wall Art Vinyl Inc., a United States, California corporation (DBA "[Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//)") under the domain name DezignWithaZ.com (the "[Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site" and registered brand name Dezign With a Z.

We respect our customers privacy and personal information we appreciate that you have chosen [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) products. We understand that you are concerned about your security, privacy and the confidentiality of information we may gain about you online. We are committed to respecting your privacy. 

Throughout this Privacy Policy we refer to your "personal information" which means information about you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your home address and home telephone number are examples of personal information. 

This Privacy Policy explains our policy for handling personal information which you provide to us as you access and interact with the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site. 

We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site, so we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. 

In addition to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, there may also be specific and additional privacy provisions which apply to certain parts of the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site. You should review such additional provisions where applicable. In the event of any inconsistency between the provisions of this Privacy Policy and those specific and additional provisions, the specific and additional provisions will prevail. 

**2\. Information collected and how we use it**  
The information about you which we may collect through the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site varies depending on how you use the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site. We will collect information through any electronic forms you submit via the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site, or other messages you send us by e-mail. 

In common with many web sites, we may collect information such as the date and time of your visit to the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site, the pages accessed and any information downloaded. This information does not identify you as an individual and is used for statistical, reporting and [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site administration and maintenance purposes only. 

Whilst you may browse some information-only areas of the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site without providing any personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the full range of services through the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site if you do not provide us with the information outlined above. 

**3\. E-Mailing Us**   
Unless otherwise stated, when you send us an e-mail, the contents of your e-mail and your e-mail address is used by us strictly to respond to your inquiry or purchase. 

**4\. Cookies**   
Like many web sites, the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site may store some information on computers which access the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, we may use cookies to recognize a browser which has previously visited the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site and customize the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site according to previous preferences and site behavior. Cookies may also be used by the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site to manage security, manage forms such as the "quote request" form and store information about the type of browser being used. With most Internet browsers, users can erase cookies from their computer's hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, some parts of the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site may not function fully for users that disallow cookies. 

**5\. Use and disclosure of information**   
We will use or disclose personal information we collect through the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site: 

  1. to provide you with products or services requested by you;

  2. where you have consented to the use or disclosure;

  3. where we have notified you of the intended use or disclosure;

  4. for the purposes for which we collected it, and for related purposes which you would reasonably expect, which may include:

\- subject to complying with the direct marketing requirements under applicable law, providing you with information relating to [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) or promotional details about products and services that may be of interest to you, unless you have previously advised us that you do not wish to be contacted for those purposes;   
[Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) ’s research (including market research), planning, service development, security, testing and risk management;   
\- the operation, administration, development or enhancement of the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site;   
\- where a third party acquires, or wishes to acquire, an interest in [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//); and  
\- where we believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency, where fraud is suspected, or where [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) is authorized, required or permitted by law to disclose the information; and  
\- as otherwise required or authorized under the law. 

We may provide personal information we collect through the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site to third parties. The types of third parties to whom we would usually disclose that personal information may include: 

  1. our service providers who assist us in providing the [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site and our products and services (for example internet and technology service providers, mail houses, call centers, and delivery companies);

  2. organizations with whom we have co-promotional arrangements (and any agents used in administering such arrangements); and

  3. our related corporate departments

In any case **_we do not provide your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes._**   

**6\. Links to other Web Sites**   
The [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//) Web Site may contain links to third party Web Sites. Any such linked Web Sites may contain their own privacy policies or statements and those third parties, and not [Dezign With a Z](http://www.dezignwithaz.com//), are responsible for informing you about their security and privacy practices. 

**7\. Security**  
We value the personal information you give us and use a number of mechanisms to protect the security and integrity of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Please note that messages you send us by e-mail are not secure. 

**8\. Access to information**  
If you wish to request access to any personal information which we hold about you as a result of our information collection practices outlined in this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the "Contact details" set out below. Please provide as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged to cover our costs of providing the information to you. 

**9\. Contact details**  
If you have any questions or feedback about privacy, or wish to make a complaint about the way in which we have handled your personal information, you may contact us as set out below: 

Web Department  
928A Van Ness Avenue  
San Francisco, Ca 94109

_Last updated: 09/09/2008_
